const STORE = [
  {
    question: 'Where was coffee first discovered?',
    answers: [
      'Brazil',
      'Columbia',
      'Ethiopia',
      'United States'
      ],
    correct: 'Ethiopia'
  },
  
  {
    question: 'Where is the corporate headquarters of Starbucks located?',
    answers: [
      'Seattle',
      'New York',
      'Boston',
      'Chicago'
     ],
    correct: 'Seattle'
  },
  
  {
    question: 'Cappuccino is made out of?',
    answers: [
      'Espresso and milk',
      'Espresso, steamed milk, and water',
      'Espresso, steamed milk, and thick milk foam',
      'Espresso, water, and thick milk foam'
      ],
    correct: 'Espresso, steamed milk, and thick milk foam'
  },
  
  {
    question: 'What are the three fundamental latte art designs?',
    answers: [
      'Bear, circle, tulip',
      'Heart, tulip, rosetta',
      'Heart, tulip, bear',
      'Heart, bear, rosetta'
      ],
    correct: 'Heart, tulip, rosetta'
  },
  
  {
    question: 'Dark roast coffees have _____ caffeine compared to lighter roast coffees.',
    answers: [
      'More',
      'Less',
      'The same',
      'Zero'
      ],
    correct: 'Less'
  },
  
  {
    question: 'What does "espresso" mean in Italian?',
    answers: [
      'Hurry up',
      'Express yourself',
      'When something is forced out',
      'When something is soaked'
      ],
    correct: 'When something is forced out'
  },
    
  {
    question: 'Where is the majority of coffee produced?',
    answers: [
     'Vietnam',
     'Columbia',
     'Ethiopia',
     'Brazil'
     ],
    correct: 'Brazil'
  },
  
  {
    question: 'New Yorkers drink almost _____ times as much coffee as the rest of the United States.',
    answers: [
      'Six',
      'Seven',
      'Eight',
      'Nine'
      ],
    correct: 'Seven'
  },
    
  {
    question: 'Why do the effects of caffeine weaken when milk is added to coffee?',
    answers: [
      'Our bodies absorb coffee much faster when it has added fat milk content, which decreases the stimulants.',
      'Our bodies absorb coffee much slower when it has added fat milk content, which decreases the stimulants.',
      'Our bodies absorb coffee much slower when it has added fat milk content, which increases the stimulants.',
      'Our bodies absorb coffee the same time when it has added fat milk content, which decreases the stimulants.'
      ],
    correct: 'Our bodies absorb coffee much slower when it has added fat milk content, which decreases the stimulants.'
  },
    
  {
    question: 'What is the most accurate definition of a Caff√© Latte',
    answers: [
      'A shot of espresso in steamed milk lightly topped with milk foam.',
      'A shot of espresso in water lightly topped with milk foam.',
      'A shot of espresso topped with a deep layer of foamed milk.',
      'Foamed whole milk marked with shots of espresso.'
    ],
    correct: 'A shot of espresso in steamed milk lightly topped with milk foam.'
  }
];